ABOUT ME

Full-stack web developer with 10+ years of experience in the healthcare field. I have always enjoyed analyzing issues presented by clients and using my knowledge to develop a plan which supports their goals. A career in web development would allow me to continue improving people's lives while having a broader impact. My attention to detail, critical thinking skills and ability to collaborate with peers allow me to solve problems effectively.

SKILLS & PROFICIENCY

Languages HTML5, CSS, SASS, JavaScript (ES6), Ruby, SQL Front-End Frameworks React, ¡Query, Ajax, Bootstrap Back-End Frameworks Node.js, Express, EJS, ERB Systems, CMS & Databases Git, PostgreSQL, npm, asdf, jekyll Testing Cypress, Mocha/Chai, Storybook, Jest, rspec, circleCl

PROJECTS

Easy Ride - A purpose built website for the Victoria Theraputic Riding Association, to allow them to schedule rides, manage payments and track progress reports. Built with React, Material UI, Rails and PostgreSQL.

Resource Wall - A SPA to save URLs & categorize them into various different topic boards. Made with jQuery, jQuery-UI, Bootstrap, SASS, Navigo, Express, PostgreSQL

Scheduler - A CRUD application for interview appointments. Build with SASS, React, express, SQL, jest, Storybook and Cypress.

Tweeter - A twitter clone single page application using CSS, HTML, JavaScript, and jQuery.

TinyApp - An application used to shorten URLs using HTML, EJS, JavaScript and Express.

EXPERIENCES

Registered Massage Therapist

- November 2017-August 2020: Cardinal Point Health Centre
- January 2013-November 2017: Cedar Hill Sport Therapy Clinic
- August 2010-March 2013: WestShore Wellness and Chiropractic
- June 2010-August 2020: Locum (short-term sick or vacation leave)

As a sole proprietor, I managed all aspects of treating the clients in collaboration with other practitioners. Starting with the intake process where I consulted with the client to understand their needs. Along with the treatments I would also be responsible for processing insurance claims and documenting the medical history in a secure and confidential manner.



Nicole Woodcock

Web Developer



woodcock.np@gmail.com



1 250 893 9293



in npwoodcock



npwxx

EDUCATION

Diploma of Web Development

Lighthouse Labs August 2020 - November 2020

Diploma in Massage Therapy

West Coast College Of Massage Therapy Jan 2008 - May 2010

LANGUAGES

English (Native)

French (Beginner)

INTERESTS

Hiking

Geocaching

Board Games & Puzzles